[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
[ SIREN BLARING ]
♪ GO, G-GO, G-GO, GO, GO ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FAST ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FASTER, FASTER,
FASTER, FASTER, FASTER ♪
♪ MOVIN’ AT THE SPEED OF SOUND,
TRY TO CHASE HEDGEHOG AROUND ♪
♪ GOT OURSELVES A SITUATION ♪
♪ STUCK IN A NEW LOCATION ♪
♪ WITHOUT ANY EXPLANATION ♪
♪ NO TALK OF RELAXATION ♪
♪ DON’T, DON’T
DON’T, DON’T, DON’T, DON’T ♪
♪ JUST GO, GO, GO, GO ♪
♪ G-G-G-GO, GO ♪
♪ N-N-N-N-N-N-NA ♪
♪ SONIC IS ON THE RUN ♪
♪ SONIC -- HE’S NUMBER ONE ♪
♪ SONIC -- HE’S COMING NEXT,
SO WATCH OUT FOR SONIC X ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FAST ♪
♪ SONIC ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FASTER, FASTER,
FASTER, FASTER, FASTER ♪
♪ GO, G-GO, G-GO
GO, GO, GO, GO ♪
♪ SONIC X ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FASTER,
GOTTA GO FAST ♪
♪ GOTTA GO FASTER, FASTER,
FASTER, FASTER ♪
♪ SONIC X ♪
WHOA!
SONIC!
AAH!
TAILS, THE PLANE’S
ON FIRE.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WE’RE GONNA SAVE SONIC.
HANG ON, AMY!
WE’RE GONNA CRASH!
I KNOW!
[ GASPS ]
KNUCKLES!
THANKS FOR SAVING US.
HMM.
WHAT’S THE MATTER
WITH HIM?
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
OVERKILL,
JUST LIKE ALWAYS.
[ SIREN BLARING ]
[ BEEPING ]
DR. EGGMAN, THE FACILITY
IS IN 100% LOCKDOWN.
WHY DOES THAT CURSED SONIC
ALWAYS GET IN MY WAY?
HE DOESN’T GET IN YOUR WAY,
DR. EGGMAN.
SONIC JUST TRIES
TO STOP YOU FROM DOING ALL
THE BAD THINGS YOU LIKE TO DO.
CHAO, CHAO!
OH, IS THAT SO?
WELL, HE’S TOO LATE
TO STOP ME THIS TIME.
ONCE I INSERT
THE LAST CHAOS EMERALD,
MY ENERGY AMPLIFIER
WILL BE INVINCIBLE.
BUT YOU CAN’T DO THAT.
CHAO, CHAO, CHAO!
THAT’S RIGHT.
SONIC WON’T LET YOU
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU’RE WRONG, CREAMY DREAMY.
HE CAN’T STOP -- AAH!
SONIC!
SONIC.
TOO LATE.
YOU’LL NEVER
STOP ME NOW, SONIC.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS TO PUSH
THIS LITTLE BUTTON.
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH, IF YOU CAN PUSH IT
BEFORE I GRAB IT.
WHY DON’T
YOU GIVE IT A TRY?
DON’T LET HIM GET AWAY!
STOP HIM, NO MATTER WHAT.
AAH!
NO! HOLD YOUR FIRE!
AAH! HERE WE GO!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
WHAT IS THAT?
IT USED
TO BE CHAOS CONTROL.
[ GROANING ]
MAN, I MUST HAVE PASSED OUT
OR SOMETHING.
OH.
HMM.
[ HORN HONKS ]
AAH!
[ HONKING CONTINUES ]
WAAA!
OH.
[ HORNS HONKING ]
WHERE AM I?
WHAT ARE
THEY ALL STARING AT?
WHAT IS THIS, HALLOWEEN?
SO THEY CAN TALK.
Man:
WHAT IS THAT THING?
Man #2: LOOKS LIKE
A BIG HEDGEHOG.
A BLUE HEDGEHOG?
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
WE BETTER GET IT OUT OF HERE.
HEY, BUDDY, WANNA RIDE WITH US
DOWN TO THE STATION?
SHOULD I CALL
FOR BACKUP?
I HAVE THREE KITTY CATS
AT HOME.
I THINK I CAN HANDLE
THIS LITTLE FELLA.
[ SMOOCHING ]
SEE THAT? THAT THING’S GOT
AN ATTITUDE -- A BAD ONE.
YEAH, WELL,
HE WON’T GET AWAY FROM ME.
HUH?
WHY, YOU LITTLE --
TAKE IT EASY. I THINK
WE CAN HANDLE THIS
WITHOUT GETTING ROUGH.
YEAH, BUT --
DUFFY, GET BEHIND HIM.
RIGHT, SARGE.
OKAY, NOW,
WHEN I SAY THE WORD,
WE’RE ALL GONNA JUMP HIM
AT ONCE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN,
IS EVERYBODY READY?
LET’S DO IT!
OKAY, SARGE,
I THINK I GOT HIS LEG.
I GOT HIM
AROUND THE NECK, SARGE!
ALL RIGHT, LET’S PULL HIM OUT
AT THE COUNT OF THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
AAH!
DON’T WORRY, SARGE.
I GOT HIM.
WHOA!
[ SIREN WAILING ]
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
WHOA!
ATTENTION, ALL UNITS.
A BLUE HEDGEHOG IS HEADED NORTH
ON CENTRAL STREET.
SHUT DOWN ALL THOROUGHFARES
LEADING INTO AND OUT
OF STATION SQUARE
AND SET UP A ROADBLOCK
JUST BEFORE THE ON-RAMP TO 101.
I’VE NEVER SEEN
A BLUE HEDGEHOG BEFORE.
HAVE YOU?
[ LAUGHS ] IT MUST BE
ONE OF THEM FANCY NEW
SPORTS CARS FROM OVERSEAS.
HEY, IF WE CATCH IT,
MAYBE THE CAPTAIN
WILL LET US DRIVE IT.
I BET IT HAS ONE OF THOSE
CUTE LITTLE HOOD ORNAMENTS
THAT LOOKS LIKE A HEDGEHOG.
[ THUD ]
I DON’T KNOW HOW I GOT HERE,
BUT I GOTTA FIND A WAY
TO GET OUT.
HEY, DID YOU SEE...
WHAT I JUST SAW?
I THINK I DID,
BUT I WISH I DIDN’T.
THEY WERE IN HOT PURSUIT,
AND IT GOT AWAY?
CAN’T THOSE CLOWNS
EVEN CATCH A HEDGEHOG?
THERE HE IS.
VISUAL CONTACT.
SUBJECT IS HEADED NORTH
ON THE CENTRAL STREET EXTENSION
ABOUT A MILE AND A HALF
FROM THE ENTRANCE TO 101.
ROGER, DELTA ONE.
UNIT 3...
SUBJECT IS HEADED
YOUR WAY.
REPEAT -- SUBJECT
IS HEADED YOUR WAY.
Man: DON’T YOU WORRY.
THIS HEDGEHOG CAN’T GET UNDER
US, AROUND US, OR THROUGH US.
WE’LL STOP HIM.
WELL, HE DIDN’T GET UNDER US,
AROUND US, OR THROUGH US.
[ LAUGHS ]
UH, THEY’RE JUST GONNA LOVE THIS
DOWN AT HEADQUARTERS.
DELTA ONE TO BASE.
I’M AFRAID THAT ROADBLOCK
DIDN’T WORK.
NO! DON’T TELL ME
IT GOT THROUGH?
OKAY.
BAD NEWS.
[ LAUGHS ]
DON’T WORRY.
I THINK WE’VE GOT
WHAT IT TAKES
TO ROUND UP
OUR FURRY LITTLE FRIEND.
SPEED TEAM,
GET READY TO ROLL.
[ SIREN BLARING ]
WHAT’S THE TEMPERATURE
OF THE ROAD SURFACE NIGHT?
IT’S ABOUT 70 DEGREES
AND DRY AS A BONE.
LIGHT BREEZE
FROM THE WEST?
ALMOST NOTHING.
ROAD --
PITTED OR SMOOTH?
NICE AND SMOOTH.
THEN LET’S SEE.
GIVE ME THE FIVE GROOVE,
MEDIUM SOFT.
HERE YOU GO.
[ BEEPING ]
I’VE PROGRAMMED GEARS FIVE
AND SIX TO FREEWAY SPEED.
GREAT.
OH, AND I FILLED THAT SECRET
FUEL TANK ON YOUR CAR
JUST LIKE YOU ASKED ME TO.
GOOD WORK.
CHIEF, THEY LAST SPOTTED THE
SUBJECT AT MILE 79 ON 101 NORTH.
ROGER.
ALL RIGHT, TEAM,
LET’S MOVE OUT.
GO.
THE SKY
LOOKS THE SAME...
SO DO THE STARS
AND THE MOON.
[ SIREN BLARING ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
I GUESS CHAOS CONTROL
MUST HAVE SENT ME HERE.
I TRAVELED THROUGH SPACE.
DID I TRAVEL
THROUGH TIME, TOO?
AM I THE ONLY ONE HERE?
[ Thinking ]
ARE ALL THE OTHERS GONE?
WELL, GUESS I’LL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH.
[ SIREN WAILING ]
HI, THERE.
YOU’RE A HARD HOG
TO KEEP UP WITH.
HEY, HOLD ON.
WE DON’T GET SUCH FAST COMPANY
VERY OFTEN.
IN FACT,
I’M GLAD YOU SHOWED UP.
THIS PLACE
IS WAY TOO PEACEFUL.
OVER THE LAST 12 MONTHS,
I’VE ONLY MADE ONE ARREST.
SOME JOKER GOT IT INTO HIS HEAD
THAT HE WAS A HOTSHOT DRIVER --
HAD HIS OWN FORMULA 1 CAR
AND EVERYTHING.
I GUESS HE THOUGHT HE’D GIVE ME
A RUN FOR MY MONEY.
BUT IT WAS ALL OVER
IN A MINUTE.
IT TOOK ME LONGER
THAN THAT TO SUIT UP.
HMM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
HE NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
OF COURSE,
IT’S OUR OWN FAULT.
THIS TOWN’S DULL
MAINLY BECAUSE OF US.
YOU SEE, WE’RE THE HIGH-SPEED
PURSUIT UNIT, THE S-TEAM.
AND I’M THE LEADER
OF THE TEAM.
THEY CALL ME
THE HIGHWAY STAR.
SO EVEN IF YOU THINK YOU’RE
THE FASTEST THING AROUND,
THINK AGAIN.
[ ENGINES TURNS OVER,
TIRES SCREECHING ]
[ Thinking ]
RUN FAST, HEDGEHOG.
I WANNA BE THE ONE
TO CATCH YOU.
HA! THE S-TEAM, EH?
THE "S" MUST STAND
FOR SLOW MOTION. [ LAUGHS ]
IT’S ACCELERATING.
BOOST YOUR REAR-WING ANGLE
TO 20 DEGREES.
ROGER.
[ BEEP ]
WELL, WELL, WELL, IT’S STARTING
TO LOOK LIKE THE RUSH HOUR.
[ Sarcastically ] OH, NO!
HOW WILL I EVER ESCAPE?
[ LAUGHS ]
WHERE IS HE?
DID I RUN HIM OVER?
HUH?
HUH?!
HEY, YOU!
THIS IS DANGEROUS!
IT’S IRRESPONSIBLE!
WHAT HAPPENS IF KIDS
START TRYING THIS?
KIDS, DON’T USE FORMULA 1
RACE CARS TO CHASE HEDGEHOGS.
YOU’RE NOT GONNA TREAT
THE S-TEAM LIKE CHUMPS.
WE’LL TEACH YOU
A LESSON.
BOOST ALL WINGS .5 DEGREES,
AND LET’S GET THIS GUY!
ROGER.
[ BEEPING ]
FULL THROTTLE!
[ BEEPING CONTINUES ]
[ GRUNTING ]
WHAT THE --
HOW CAN --
IT’S PLAYING WITH US!
WHERE’D THIS THING
COME FROM?
CHIEF, YOU GOT
TO DO SOMETHING!
PLAYTIME
IS NOW OFFICIALLY OVER.
ATTENTION, ALL UNITS.
OPEN THE CENTER LINE.
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
I DIDN’T THINK
I’D HAVE TO DO THIS,
BUT I HAVE NO CHOICE.
I WILL NOT HAVE ANYBODY
FASTER THAN ME
ON MY HIGHWAY.
[ BEEPING ]
[ LAUGHS ] THE ONLY WAY
HE CAN BEAT ME NOW
IS IF HE GOES SUPERSONIC.
[ LAUGHS ]
A SONIC BOOM!
HE’S MOVING FASTER
THAN THE SPEED OF SOUND.
CHIEF, YOU’RE RUNNING OUT
OF ROAD!
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
OH.
MAYBE THIS PLACE
ISN’T SO BAD.
AT LEAST I KNOW SOMEBODY
I CAN HAVE FUN WITH.
OH!
A-A POOL?!
[ CHUCKLES ]
UH-OH.
[ GRUNTING ]
SEE YA!
[ Muffled ] HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
[ COUGHING ]
THAT WAS CLOSE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ GRUNTS ] YEAH.
THANKS A LOT.
I DIDN’T THINK
YOU COULD TALK.
I CAN DO A LOT
OF THINGS.
WOW! THAT’S AWESOME...
T-THAT YOU CAN TALK,
I MEAN.
MY NAME’S CHRISTOPHER.
DO YOU HAVE A NAME?
YEAH, I HAVE A NAME.
MY NAME
IS SONIC THE HEDGEHOG.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
4KIDS PRODUCTIONS, INC.